ghxclusives.com 2012-11-14

# Privacy | GhXclusives

GhXclusives takes your privacy seriously. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice is available on our homepage.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how GhXclusives treats personal information that GhXclusives collects and receives, including information related to your past use of GhXclusives  products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that GhXclusives does not own or control, or to people that GhXclusives does not employ or manage. In addition, certain GhXclusives associated companies have their own privacy statements.

**Information Collection and Use General**

GhXclusives collects personal information when you register with GhXclusives, when you use GhXclusives products or services, when you visit GhXclusivespages or the pages of certain GhXclusives partners.GhXclusives may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with GhXclusives  and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. GhXclusives collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer. GhXclusives automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, GhXclusives cookie information, and the page you request. GhXclusives uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Children**

GhXclusives does not allow a child under age 13 to register for any GhXclusives  services. GhXclusives does not ask a child under age 13 for any personal information.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

GhXclusives does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with GhXclusives under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help GhXclusives communicate with you about offers from GhXclusives and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of GhXclusives’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We transfer information about you if GhXclusives is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, GhXclusives will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. GhXclusives displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria – for example, men ages 16-24 from a particular geographic area. GhXclusives does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. GhXclusives works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

**Cookies**

GhXclusives  may set and access GhXclusivescookies on your computer. GhXclusives  lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to GhXclusives’s cookies. GhXclusives uses web beacons to access GhXclusives cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with GhXclusives products and services.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

You can edit your GhXclusives Account Information, at any time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the GhXclusives service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the GhXclusives Newsletter, that are considered part of your GhXclusives account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. You can delete your GhXclusives account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

**Confidentiality and Security**

GhXclusives limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**
